<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>
    <Operation Class="VEF.PatchOperationToggableSequence">
        <enabled>False</enabled>
        <mods>
            <li>Warhammer 40.000 - Genes</li>
        </mods>
        <label>Reduce psyker mood debuff:</label>
        <operations>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName = "BEWH_IotaPsyker"]</xpath>
                <value>
                    <stages>
                        <li>
                            <label>Iota Psyker</label>
                            <description>The Warp hums softly within me, a faint whisper rather than a roar. My connection is limited, but sufficient. I wield this power with precision and restraint, knowing I walk a finer line than most.</description>
                            <baseMoodEffect>-1</baseMoodEffect>
                        </li>
                    </stages>
                </value>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName = "BEWH_EpsilonPsyker"]</xpath>
                <value>
                    <stages>
                        <li>
                            <label>Epsilon Psyker</label>
                            <description>The warp flows through me, steady and strong. Its whispers guide me, its power fuels me, yet I remain vigilant.</description>
                            <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
                        </li>
                    </stages>
                </value>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName = "BEWH_DeltaPsyker"]</xpath>
                <value>
                    <stages>
                        <li>
                            <label>Delta Psyker</label>
                            <description>The warp surges within me, potent and commanding. Its tides are fierce, but I have the strength to harness them. Though the temptation of chaos is ever-present, my resolve keeps me steadfast.</description>
                            <baseMoodEffect>-4</baseMoodEffect>
                        </li>
                    </stages>
                </value>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName = "BEWH_BetaPsyker"]</xpath>
                <value>
                    <stages>
                        <li>
                            <label>Beta Psyker</label>
                            <description>The warp is a storm within me, vast and unrelenting. I wield a power few can comprehend, let alone control. Every thought, every action must be precise, for my power hovers on the brink of destruction. Yet I am no mere instrument of the Immaterium - I am its master.</description>
                            <baseMoodEffect>-7</baseMoodEffect>
                        </li>
                    </stages>
                </value>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>Defs/ThoughtDef[defName = "BEWH_AlphaPsyker"]</xpath>
                <value>
                    <stages>
                        <li>
                            <label>Alpha Psyker</label>
                            <description>The warp bends to my will, its infinite power coursing through me like a roaring tempest. I am a living beacon of the Immaterium, my abilities far beyond what mortals can fathom. Such power is both a blessing and a burden, for even the slightest misstep could obliterate worlds.</description>
                            <baseMoodEffect>-11</baseMoodEffect>
                        </li>
                    </stages>
                </value>
            </li>
        </operations>
    </Operation>
</Patch>